<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-07-06T19:54:35-07:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">My Daily Walk with the Lord</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">How to have happy home</title><link href="/2017/07/01/how-to-have-happy-home.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to have happy home" /><published>2017-07-01T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-07-01T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>/2017/07/01/how-to-have-happy-home</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/07/01/how-to-have-happy-home.html">&lt;p&gt;Unless the LORD builds the house, the builders labor in vain. Psalm 127-1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three things for husband and wife must do: 
1) Salvation - Marriage are two sinners put together. Ephesians 2 says we all have sinned and followed the ways of the world. Imagine having two people living in the same roof. But because of God’s love to us, we are saved. Ephesians 2:8-9 says, “For it is by grace you have been saved, through faith—and this is not from yourselves, it is the gift of God— not by works, so that no one can boast”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Spirit Filled or Yield to Spirit – “Wake up, sleeper, rise from the dead, and Christ will shine on you.” Ephesians 5:14-18&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a) Born of Spirit
b) Walk in Spirit
-Result if filled with Spirit (Ephesians 5:19)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Thankfulness – “Always giving thanks to God the Father for everything, in the name of our Lord Jesus Christ. Ephesians 5:20
2) Submissive - Submit to one another out of reverence for Christ. Ephesians 5:21
3) Submissive Obedience – Found in God’s word
For Wives: Wives, submit yourselves to your own husbands as you do to the Lord. For the husband is the head of the wife as Christ is the head of the church, his body, of which he is the Savior. Now as the church submits to Christ, so also wives should submit to their husbands in everything. Ephesians 5:22:24&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you submit?
a) Love – Then they can urge the younger women to love their husbands and children, 
Titus 2:4
b) Submit – Ephesians 5:22-24
c) Reverence or respect - However, each one of you also must love his wife as he loves himself, and the wife must respect her husband. Ephesians 5:33
For Husband: Husbands, love your wives, just as Christ loved the church and gave himself up for her 26 to make her holy, cleansing[b] her by the washing with water through the word, 27 and to present her to himself as a radiant church, without stain or wrinkle or any other blemish, but holy and blameless. 28 In this same way, husbands ought to love their wives as their own bodies. He who loves his wife loves himself. 29 After all, no one ever hated their own body, but they feed and care for their body, just as Christ does the church— 30 for we are members of his body.31 “For this reason a man will leave his father and mother and be united to his wife, and the two will become one flesh.” Ephesians 5:25-31&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you love your wife?
a) Unconditionally -Ephesians 5: 25
b) Sacrificially - Ephesians 5: 25
c) Sanctifying – Ephesians 5:26 -27
d) Exclusively - Ephesians 5:31
e) Sincerely 
f) Dwell to wife - Husbands, in the same way be considerate as you live with your wives, and treat them with respect as the weaker partner and as heirs with you of the gracious gift of life, so that nothing will hinder your prayers. 1 Peter 3:7
g) Honor her highly - Husbands, in the same way be considerate as you live with your wives, and treat them with respect as the weaker partner and as heirs with you of the gracious gift of life, so that nothing will hinder your prayers. 1 Peter 3:7&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Children: Children, obey your parents in the Lord, for this is right. 2 “Honor your father and mother”—which is the first commandment with a promise—3 “so that it may go well with you and that you may enjoy long life on the earth. Ephesians 6:1-3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What children must do: 
1) Obey – V1
2) Honor – V2
3) Then it will go well – V3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Parents: And, ye fathers, provoke not your children to wrath: but bring them up in the nurture 
and admonition of the Lord. Ephesians 6:4&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What parents must do: 
1) Love them tenderly – Found in “Bring them up”
2) Discipline them consistently – Found in “nurture”
3) Instruct them wisely – Found in “admonition of the Lord”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Craig Lucas</name></author><category term="jekyll test" /><category term="liquid" /><category term="blogging" /><summary type="html">Unless the LORD builds the house, the builders labor in vain. Psalm 127-1</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome To Jekyll</title><link href="/2017/06/24/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome To Jekyll" /><published>2017-06-24T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-06-24T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>/2017/06/24/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/06/24/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;layout: post
title:  “Welcome to Jekyll!”
date:   2017-06-24 14:11:11 -0700
categories: jekyll update
tags:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;jekyll&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;liquid&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;blogging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">layout: post title: “Welcome to Jekyll!” date: 2017-06-24 14:11:11 -0700 categories: jekyll update tags: jekyll liquid blogging</summary></entry></feed>